<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

   <statements version="1.0" htmlParse="false">
     <statement id="1">1.	In a course like this, I prefer review material that really challenges me so I can learn new things that may be asked on the board exam.</statement>
     <statement id="2">2.	If I study in appropriate ways, then I will be able to learn enough to pass boards.</statement>
     <statement id="3">3.	When I take an exam like the ones in this course, I think about how poorly I am doing compared with other students.</statement>
     <statement id="4">4.	I'm certain I can master the review material presented in this course.</statement>
     <statement id="5">5.	Getting a good grade on the mock board is the most satisfying thing for me right now.</statement>
     <statement id="6">6.	When I take exams such as these in this course, I think about items on other parts of the exam I am struggling to answer.</statement>
     <statement id="7">7.	It is my own fault if I don't learn the important material required for boards.</statement>
     <statement id="8">8.	It is important for me to learn the material reviewed in this course. </statement>
     <statement id="9">9.	The most important thing is passing the board exam really well.</statement>
     <statement id="10">10.	I'm confident I can understand the basic concepts taught in this board prep course.</statement>
     <statement id="11">11.	If I can, I want to get better grades on the mock board exam than other students in the class.</statement>
     <statement id="12">12.	When I take exams that emulate the board exam, I think of the consequences of failing.</statement>
     <statement id="13">13.	I prefer course material that will arouse my curiosity, even if it is difficult to learn.</statement>
     <statement id="14">14.	I am very interested in the content area of this course. </statement>
     <statement id="15">15.	If I try hard enough, then I will understand all the material required for boards.</statement>
     <statement id="16">16.	I have an uneasy, upset feeling when I take an exam that relates to the board exam.</statement>
     <statement id="17">17.	The most satisfying thing for me is trying to understand the content as thoroughly as possible.</statement>
     <statement id="18">18.	Understanding the subject matter reviewed in this course is very important to me.</statement>
     <statement id="19">19.	I feel my heart beating fast when I take an exam.</statement>
     <statement id="20">20.	I want to do well in this course because it is important to show my ability to my family, friends, or others.</statement>
     <statement id="21">21.	I believe I will receive an excellent grade on the mock board exam.</statement>
     <statement id="22">22.	I'm certain I can understand the most difficult concepts reviewed in this course.</statement>
     <statement id="23">23.	When studying for boards, I often try to explain the material to a classmate or a friend.</statement>
     <statement id="24">24.	I often feel so lazy or bored when I study that I quit before I finish what I planned to do.</statement>
     <statement id="25">25.	Even if I have trouble learning the material for boards, I try to do the work on my own, without help from anyone.</statement>
     <statement id="26">26.	I try to work with other students to study for the board exam.</statement>
     <statement id="27">27.	I am working hard to do well even if I don't like what I am studying.</statement>
     <statement id="28">28.	When studying, I often set aside time to discuss the course material with a group of students from the class.</statement>
     <statement id="29">29.	When I can't understand the material, I am supposed to be studying, I ask another student in this class for help</statement>
     <statement id="30">30.	I ask the instructor to clarify concepts I don't understand well.</statement>
     <statement id="31">31.	When course work is difficult, I give up or only study the easy parts.</statement>
     <statement id="32">32.	When I study concepts for the board exam, I outline the material to help me organize my thoughts.</statement>
     <statement id="33">33.	During class time I often miss important points because I’m thinking of other things</statement>
     <statement id="34">34.	Even when materials I'm studying are dull and uninteresting, I manage to keep working until I finish the section.</statement>
     <statement id="35">35.	When working through material, I make up questions to help focus my thoughts.</statement>
     <statement id="36">36.	When I become confused about something I'm studying, I go back and try to figure it out.</statement>
     <statement id="37">37.	When I study, I go through my class notes and try to find the most important ideas.</statement>
     <statement id="38">38.	I make good use of my study time.</statement>
     <statement id="39">39.	If course materials are difficult to understand, I change the way I approach the material.</statement>
     <statement id="40">40.	When studying for boards, I read my class handouts over and over.</statement>
     <statement id="41">41.	When a theory, interpretation, or conclusion is presented in class or in the readings, I try to decide if there is good supporting evidence.</statement>
     <statement id="42">42.	I make simple charts, diagrams, concept maps or tables to help me organize the material.</statement>
     <statement id="43">43.	When I study for a class, I pull together information from different sources, such as lectures, readings, and external sources.</statement>
     <statement id="44">44.	I often find that I have been reading but don't have a clue as to what it was all about</statement>
     <statement id="45">45.	I memorize key words to remind me of important concepts when I study.</statement>
     <statement id="46">46.	When learning new material, I try to relate the material to what I already know.</statement>
     <statement id="47">47.	I usually study for boards in a regular place where I can concentrate on my course work.</statement>
     <statement id="48">48.	When I study, I write brief summaries of the main ideas and concepts from the lectures.</statement>
     <statement id="49">49.	I try to understand the material presented in classes by making connections between the lectures.</statement>
     <statement id="50">50.	I make sure I keep up my weekly board prep schedule.</statement>
     <statement id="51">51.	Whenever I read or hear an assertion or conclusion in this review course, I think about possible alternatives.</statement>
     <statement id="52">52.	When I study, I make lists of important terms and memorize the list.</statement>
     <statement id="53">53.	I often find that I don't spend much time on board prep because of other activities.</statement>
     <statement id="54">54.	I try to apply ideas from readings in one course to understand topics in another course that need to be studied for the mock board. </statement>
   </statements>